Hope he's right, because if he's not,
it'll cost him one of his three timeouts.
(Penny:)You know, Leonard, honey...
(Penny:)...I wouldn't mind if you wanted
to go fly kites with Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I'll watch the end of the game.
There's three minutes left.
Until halftime.
(Leonard:)This is just half?
(Leonard:)We've been here for hours.
(Penny:)-You're gonna be here for a couple more.
-Oh, you're kidding.
(Sheldon:)-No.
-Nice meeting all of you.
(Penny:)So, yeah, anyway,
that's my boyfriend.
(Penny:)He is really smart.
(Raj:)I really like my saber-toothed cat.
Thank you.
(Howard:)My pleasure.
(Howard:)Maybe after lunch we can go
to Marie Callender's and have some pie.
(Raj:)-I'd like that.
-Heh.
[SIGHS]